Guide to the John D. Wirth Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
John D. Wirth papers
1952-2002
SC0660
Wirth, John D.
40 Linear feet
Collection consists largely of professional papers from his academic life, including course materials, correspondence, reports, research files, minutes, memos, and others. Subject matter includes Latin American studies, environmental history, and his service as Vice-Provost at Stanford.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
John D. Wirth was the Gildred Professor of Latin American Studies at Stanford University at the time of his death in 2002. He earned his bachelor's degree at Harvard University in 1958 and his doctorate at Stanford in Latin American history in 1967. He joined the Stanford faculty in 1965; his administrative positions included director of the Latin American Studies center, 1975-1983 and 2000-2001, and Vice Provost for Academic Planning and Development, 1988-1991. His scholarly interests included Brazilian studies, North American history, and environmental relationships among Mexico, Canada, and the United States.
Description of the Collection
Collection consists largely of professional papers from his academic life, including course materials, correspondence, reports, research files, minutes, memos, and others. Subject matter includes Latin American studies, environmental history, and his service as Vice-Provost at Stanford.
Access Terms
Wirth, John D.; Environmental management.; Human ecology --History.; Latin America--Study and teaching
Collection Contents
- Original Accession, Accession ARCH-2002-288
  - Photocopy of memo: Confidencial. Informacao Para o Senhor Presidente da Republica, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Photocopy: "A Reporter at Large Great Plains-III" New Yorker March 6, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Press material on the film Gaijin, A Brazilian Odyssey (Box 1)
  - Photocopy: Reliving the Past, The Worlds of Social History, edited by Olivier Zunz, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Tss paper: "Legal Education and the Brazilian Crisis" by Francisco Clementino de San Tiago Danta, translated by David M. Trubek, June 1973 (Box 1)
  - Scott Mainwaring, The Transition to Democracy in Brazil; Working Paper #66 March 1986, Kellogg Institute for International Studies (Box 1)
  - Photocopy from book: Bolton, Boltonism, and Neo-Boltonism (Box 1)
  - Notebook from his graduate studies, 1961-65: French history (Box 1)
  - Notebook from his graduate studies, 1961-65: Latin American students (Box 1)
  - Notebook from his graduate studies, 1961-65: Latin American history (Box 1)
  - Notebook from his graduate studies, 1961-65: Brazilian political history (Box 1)
  - Articles of interest saved by JDW (Box 1)
  - Articles of interest saved by JDW (Box 1)
  - Environmental history and policy (Hist. 281V – syllabus and sources) 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - North/South (published papers on economic relations between North and South Americ) 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - MERCOSUR (notes) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Brazil and NAFTA (published items and some correspondence, mostly re talk by Wirth) 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper: Mission from Canada Nov. 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NAFTA and MERCOSUR, History 181V, syllabus and sources, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - NAFTA and MERCOSUR class, handouts (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Paper by Silvia Cappelli, "O Direito Ambiental Brasilleiro" ca. 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Spiral bound reader for Nafta-Mercosur (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Syllabi from other professors' courses on Nafta and Mercosur (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chile readings (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous items on Mercosur (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Envelope of clippings (not in English) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Native Americas, Akwe:kon's Journal of Indigenous Issues, Fall 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Spiral bound publication: Proyeccion del Debate Medioambiental. Hacia un Nuevo Movimiento Social en Chile? (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chile Canada Agreement on Environmental Cooperation (not in English) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Publication: manual de vigilancia ambiental (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Clippings (not in English) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Clippings (not in English) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Pablo Camus and Ernst R. Hajek, "Historia ambiental de Chile" 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Several papers on ecological issues in Latin America (not in English) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Envelope: Mining News, Nov. 1998 (Latin American edition) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Envelope: La Tercera, Jueves 21 de enero de 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Paper by Nicole Fischer, "Role of State Owned Companies and Transnational Corporations in the Sustainable Development of Chile," 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Assorted items on NAFTA: articles and memoranda (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Public Consultation on Revised Version of "Guidelines for Submissions on Enforcement Matters under Articles 14 and 15 of the North American Agreement on Environmental Cooperation" Exectuve Summar of Comments Received (1998) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Assorted publications, clippings, some of which are from the Commission for Environmental Cooperation (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bound item: North American Agenda for Action: 1999-2001. A Three-Year Program Plan for the Commission for Environmental Cooperation (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Proposed Annual Program and Budget 1999. Commission for Environmental Cooperation. Version 1 (Oct. 1998) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Copy of thesis by Lise Fernanda Sedrez, "A Meeting of Minds: Coalitions, Presentations and American Non-governmental Organizations in the Brazilian Amazon" May 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - TED Case Studies. Chilean Forest Preservation and the Project River Condor [internet printed] (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - El Proyecto Pumalin. Informe Tecnico Puerot Montt, Junio de 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lower Rio Grande Valley Environmental Monitoring Study Report to the Community on the Pilot Project June 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Two miscellaneous papers (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - On Track? Sustainability and the State of the North American Environment. Draft pre-publication manuscript Nov. 4, 1998. Commission for Environmental Cooperation (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - An Analytic Framework for Assessing Environmental Effects of the north American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA): Phase II. [draft] Commission for Environmental Cooperation (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Feedlot Production of Cattle in the United States and Canada: Some Environmental Implications of the North American Free Trade Agreement. [draft] Commission for Environmental Cooperation (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Electricity in North America: Some Environmental Implications of the North American Free Trade Agreement. [draft] Commission for Environmental Cooperation (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Assorted reports and draft reports of the CEC, pertinent to NAFTA, biodiversity conservation, air pollution (Box 3)
  - North American Institute publications: History and National Identity (edited by JDW) 1994; Harmonizing Economic Competitiveness with Environmental Quality: A North American Challenge 1991; and Citizens, Networks and New Institutions in the North American Community 1994 (Box 3)
  - North American Youth Service, correspondence 2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Report of the External Review Committee to the Vanderbilt History Department March 12-14, 2000 [JDW was on the committee] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bound item: typescript of a novel? (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Envelope: note cards (smoke damaged) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Clippings re Canadian gas, 1984-87 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bibliographic materials re Canadian energy (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sources, correspondence, miscellany re Wirth's research on electricity marketing among Pacific Northwest regions, 1987 [smoke damage] (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Herriott, Scott Robert, "The Political Economy of Partnerships with Applications to Power Pooling in the Electric Utility Industry" Institute for Energy Studies Report No. 53, June 1984 [smoke damage] (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - "Integracion Electrica en American del Sur", Ing. Roman Berro C., 1976 [smoke damage] (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Trinational Energy Policy Workshop [proceedings] Feb. 12 and 13, 1987, Stanford University [smoke damage] (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - International river systems and boundaries, clippings, 1986-87 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Assorted papers (unpublished) on policy issues and perspectives on North American natural gas trade, 1983 [smoke damage] (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Two reports from North American Electric Reliability Council on electric supply and demand, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Lydia Sigaud, Efeitos Sociais de Grandes Projetos Hidreletricos: As Barragens de Sobradinho e Machadinho, 1986 [smoke damage] (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Papers from the gas trade workshop at Stanford, 1985 [smoke damage] (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Assorted papers on NAFTA 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Gary C. Hufbauer et. al., NAFTA and the Environment: Seven Years Later (Box 3)
  - 0 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - North American Environmental Law and Policy, North American Boundary and Transboundary Inland Water Management Report, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - North American Symposium on Understanding the Linkages between Trade and Environment, Oct. 2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - North American Institute, The North American Environment: Opportunities for Trinational Cooperation by Canada, the United States, and Mexico. Report and Recommendations, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Two papers by Gary Hufbauer: "Vision for NAFTA: A Common Frontier?" and "North American Labor under NAFTA" (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Issue Study 3. Electricity in North America: Some Environmental Implications of the North American Free Trade Agreement (Box 3)
  - Hard Issues, Innovative Approaches: Improving NGO-Industry Dialogue on Corporate Responsibility and Accountability, Report of the Roundtable, Nov. 9, 1999 Stanford University (Box 3)
  - Written Comments on the Public History of Submissions made under Articles 14 and 15 of the North American Agreement on Environmental Cooperation (as 31 January 2001) (Box 3)
  - North American Agenda for Action: 2001-2003; A Three-Year Program Plan for the North American Commission on Environmental Cooperation, November 2000 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous – correspondence and notes (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "Lessons Learned: Citizen Submissions under Articles 14 and 15 of the North American Agreement on Environmental Cooperation. Draft Report to the Council of the North American Commission on Environmental Cooperation" March 2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - CEC Evaluation Framework – 2 publications (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Three papers on precaution prepared for the North American Commission on Environmental Cooperation, 2001, with cover memo, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 0
  - John Wirth – contains assorted CEC items on children's health and the environment and other projects (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CEC, Joint Public Advisory Committee – correspondence and memos, 2000-2002, and a paper by Wirth "If so, then what? The struggle for TEIA" 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Copy of master's thesis by Jim Sussex, "Towards an effective transboundary environmental impact assessment regime for North America" 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CEC. Report of the Executive Director Commisson for Environmental Cooperation Regular Session of the CEC Council, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - John Wirth – contains memos, agenda, etc. for JPAC meeting Oct. 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CEC assorted memos, reports (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 2002-2004 Proposed Program Plan and Budget for the Commission for Environmental Cooperation of North America, Sept. 2001 (Box 4)
  - 2001-2003 Proposed Program Plan and Budget for the North American Commission for Environmental Cooperation, August 2000 (Box 4)
  - Materials for National and Government Advisory Committees to the U.S. Representative to the CEC, San Diego, CA, Sept. 2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Letters received by Wirth at North American Institute, 1995-97 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Lessons Learned: Citizen Submissions under Articles 14 and 15 of the North American Agreement on Environmental Cooperation. Final Report to the Council of the North American Commission on Environmental Cooperation" June 2001 (Box 4)
  - CEC. Ribbon of Life; An agenda for preserving transboundary migratory bird habitat on the upper San Pedro River, 1999 (Box 4)
  - JPAC meetings: council minutes, agendas, faxes, correspondence, 1996-97 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Nicole T. Carter – research proposal, correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Binder: North America Forum "The New Economic Geography of North America: Regions and Cities in Transition" workshop, Stanford University, Feb. 1995 (Box 4)
  - "Bibliografia Anotada: Oranizacoes nao-governamentais e congeners que atuam nos setores menor, saude e nutricao," 1990 (Box 4)
  - "Analise do papel da organizacoes nao-goernamentais na implementacao das politicas publicas" Volume 2B, parte II (Box 4)
  - Papers and reports re the Cuixmala Model Draft Treaty 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Greg Matter Publishing (re proposal for digitizing NAFTA materials by Stanford University Libraries) 1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - San Antonio – correspondence re arranging luncheon with Ambassador Herzog, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Assorted papers for conference on Latin American History 1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Paper by Joachim Blatter (Cross-border cooperation and sustainable development in Europe and North America) with cover letter to Wirth, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Capitulo II. "Avaliacao da prestacao de services de organizacoes nao-governamentais que atendem criancas, adolescents e idosos" (Box 4)
  - "Analise do papel das organizacoes nao governamentais – ong's na implementacao de politicas publicas" (Box 4)
  - Letter from Wirth to Dr. A. W. Rasporich, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hidrovia conservation (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Wirth, "Advancing the North American Community," 1996 with other articles not by Wirth (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Assorted articles on Brazil and one Stanford student paper (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Changing land use – assorted articles and clippings (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Copy of Wirth's "Canadians and Americans Confront Transboundary Pollution 1927-41", letter to Wirth from Stephen Bell, and copy of an article by John Kirby (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Seminars/Forms – [actually contains miscellaneous correspondence and other items unrelated to folder title] (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Creation of North America, History 276/376 – syllabus and sources (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - envelope: note cards (Box 4)
  - Materials from workshop Smoke and Mirrors and Wirth's notes, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - John Wirth, contains draft of "If So, then What? The Struggle for TEIA," paper presented at Smoke and Mirrors workshop and related correspondence (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Purkey and Mansfield, Estimating the Potential for in lieu Conjunctive Water Management in the Central Valley of California, February 2002 (Box 4)
  - The American Society for Environmental History Annual Meeting 2002, "Producing and Consuming Natures" (Box 4)
  - North American Agenda for Action: 2002-2004. A Three-Year Program Plan for the Commission for Environmental Cooperation of North America. December 2001 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous: "Perspectives on the JPAC" by Wirth, 2002; personal financial notes; clipping (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Brazil documents 1960s-1980s (some class files, some sources; includes correspondence with General Ibá) (Box 5)
  - Supporting articles for research (Box 6)
  - Papers for comment (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous files [original box unlabelled] including class files and a file on Tangiers with photos and maps (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous files [original box unlabelled] continued (Box 7)
  - Dissertations by students at other universities (Box 7)
  - Files re students, students – Chile, Latin American Studies, LAS searches, Committee on International Studies, and individuals by name. Files include correspondence, papers, clippings, 1984-1999. (Box 8)
  - Professional files and course files 1979-1983 (Box 9)
  - Slides: La Gavia (Mexico?), reproductions of historic images, and others (Box 9)
  - Assorted publications re Latin America (Box 9)
  - Rose Hayden, "Brazil Diary" typescript, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Articles, papers, and other source materials mostly on Brazil (Box 9)
  - Latin American Bibliography, prepared for the working Group on the State and Public Policy Committee on Latin American Studies. Institute of International Studies, UC Berkeley, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Richardo A. Silva, "Le Bresil de Getulio Vargas et la Formation des blocs: 1930-1942" (thesis 1981) and correspondence, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Typescript with corrections/changes of a work by JDW (Box 9)
  - UC Berkeley, Proposal for Canadian Studies Chair (Box 10)
  - Binder (JDW as Vice provost for Academic Planning and Development) – Fund raising approvals 1985-89 (Box 10)
  - Binder (JDW as Vice provost for Academic Planning and Development) – Provost's Advisory Group, agendas and supporting documents for meetings 1987-1991 (Box 10)
  - Worth, J. D. and Robert L. Earle, eds. North American Identities – final draft, 1993 [binder] (Box 10)
  - JDW articles (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bidwell/Pritchard (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence 1976-2002 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Slenes, Robert W. "Slave Population and Society in Nineteenth-Century Brazil: New Sources and a Proposal for Research" (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Photocopied source: Recanto de Sertao (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - History LA Grad. Program (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - SU business (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - LAS-School of Education joint discussions (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - LAS undergraduate major (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Boris Fausto – letter to, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Jose Carlos Sebe – correspondence 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Conniff – Comparative Populism Volume (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Regionalist Project – translations, last phase (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Grants 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Grant information (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Robert Levine correspondence 1971-72 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Joint letters, Regionalist Project, sent 1971 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Footnotes/bibliography (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Repression in Brazil (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Foreign scholars impact (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Research plans (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Latin American Studies (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - NSF – Regionalist Project (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Stanford and history department (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Photocopy: article by I. Horowitz (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Reviews (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - [Bibliography for dissertation] (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - SSRC Grant Request HEW 1966-67 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Guide to historical literature (bibliography and correspondence) 1965-66 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - New Orleans paper, SHA, Nov. 1968 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Brazilian Congress documents [Xeroxed catalog cards] (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - SSRC 1968 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - NDEA Proposal [MG] (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - CRIS Proposals to outside (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Humanities Foundation – Regionalist Project (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - LA Town Hall 1972 [re talk] (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Grants - JDW for Regionalist Project (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Regionalist Project – comments on/suggestions (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - J. L. Love – research proposal (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - General file of statements – Regionalist Project (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Comparative Regionalism 1968 (May) Working Session (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Comparative Regional Development First Proposal 1966 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Comparative Regional Development Schmitter critique, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Current correspondence, Regionalist Project, 1968-69 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - [McGraw-Hill Encyclopedia of World Biography – correspondence 1969] (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - SHA, New Orleans Nov. 1968 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Institute of Contemporary History, Cleantho de Paiva Leite, 1967-68 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Minnesota, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - CLAH [Conference on Latin American History] – Brazilianists (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Guide to Hist. Lit. (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - [PCB Symposium on Brazilian History, 1968] (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Students – U.S. (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Donald Warren Griffin, The Normal Years: Brazilian-American Relations 1930-1939 [typed notes re this dissertation] (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Aguirre, Jesse [actually contains correspondence with Marta Cehelsky, 1969] (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Map of Rio (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - [Stephan Weissman reference letters/info 1968 – in envelope not folder] (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - [Record of book buying in Brazil for SUL] (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - John Wirth, "Latin American Students," History 340, Dec. 7, 1961 [pressboard binder] (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - History 282, syllabus 1967 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Ivan Andras Lakos, The effects of Brazil's foreign exchange policy…, notes on (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Warren Kempton Dean, Sao Paul's Industrial Elite, 1890-1960 – notes on (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Comparative Development seminar – mostly correspondence 1966 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Nathaniel H. Leff, Economic Policy and Economic Development in Brazil, 1947-1964 – notes on this manuscript (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Ph.D. exams (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - James W. Wilkie, "Postulates of the Oral History Center for Latin America" [Ohio State] (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - [Unlabelled correspondence] (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - [John D. Wirth, "Student Politics in Brazil: An Approach," 1964 and course syllabus] (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - LAS trip Oct. 12-19, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Barman, Roderick. Brazil research proposal (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Brazilianist nominating committee (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Luso-Brazilian Review (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Luso-Brazilian Review 1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Baer translation of Villela & Suzigan book – correspondence 1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - CLAH – Socialist relations (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - CLAH nominations 1968 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - CLAH nominations 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - SU microfilm and census (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - USNA, USS Corp, GSA correspondence – German films list (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - USN Archives – Dip Records ordered by SU (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - National Archives, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - SU Library – LA holdings (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - GDR Archives and institutes (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Brazilian Law Library at L. A. County Law Library (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - [Unlabelled correspondence re SU history department 1971] (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Brazilian films (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Brazil, services (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Lei de Diretrizes e Bases da Educacao 1961 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Unfoldered materials re SU Graduate Studies Committee 1986-87 (Box 12)
  - Original, photocopied, and transcribed sources on Brazil (Box 12)
  - Manuscript of "Politics of Brazilian Development" (Box 12)
  - Vice-Provost Files
    - JW's short CV (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Italian American conference (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Italian conference (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Appointment book 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Appointment book 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Chrons, 1988 Sep (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Chrons, 1988 Oct (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Chrons, 1988 Nov (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Chrons, 1988 Dec (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Chrons, 1989 Jan (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Chrons, 1989 Feb (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Chrons, 1989 Mar (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Chrons, 1989 Apr (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Chrons, 1989 May (Box 13, Folder 14)